Guide to the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012.
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records,
- Series I: Administrative Files
  - Todd Plank Files
    - GAGV Brochure, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 73)
    - Volunteer Handbook, Undated (Box 54, Folder 74)
    - Todd Plank: Correspondence, Notes, Memos, Fliers, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 75)
    - Todd Plank: Correspondence, Memos, Fliers, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence, Notes & Hand Outs, 2003-2005 (Box 54, Folder 77)
      Primarily deals with speaking engagements
    - Volunteer Correspondence, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Todd Plank: Correspondence, Notes, Memos, Fliers, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      Marriage and family
    - Todd Plank: Correspondence & Memos (1), 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Todd Plank: Correspondence & Memos (2), 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Todd Plank: Incoming Correspondence, April-May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence -- General, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, Undated; CD-2205 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence & Fliers, Undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Intro to Ethics, Undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Course taken by Todd Plank
    - Evaluation and Test Forms, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Speaker Evaluation Forms, 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Presentations, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Workshop/Training Materials, Undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - The Power of Training, Undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - The Northwest Network, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - GLSEN: Student Harassment and Inclusion, Undated (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Domestic Violence Programs, Undated (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Teaching Respect, 1999-2001 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - "Creating a Culture of Tolerance, Value, and Respect for LGBT Persons" Talk, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Coming Out Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Culture 1.3.5, October 20, 2003; CD-2367 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - "Building Community Support for Recovery & Health" Conference, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Hall of Justice, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Hall of Justice Evaluations, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Sex Education, Undated (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Corporate Advocacy Workshop, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Transgender/Workplace, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - GAGV Presentations, Undated (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Power Point Presentation, Undated (Box 55, Folder 30)
      Preparation for presentation on straight allies
    - Todd Plank: Correspondence, Notes, Memos, 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Follow Up, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Loose Ends, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Youth, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Empty Closet Rates, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Gay News, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Todd's Materials, 2001, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Program Committee Minutes, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - 30 Year Anniversary Surveys, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Referral Sources, Undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - GAGV Contact Info Questionnaire Form, Undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Faxable Flyers/Brochures, Undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Referrals Request Forms, Undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Mental Illness, Undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - The Closet: Psychological Issues of Being In and Coming Out, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      Article by Jack Drescher, M.D.
    - GAGV Programs, Undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Library & Book Related, 2003-2005 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Book Catalogs, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Film, Video, and Album Catalogs and Press Releases, 2003-2005 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - GAGV Library & Archive, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Spring Library & Archives, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - "Motor Feb. 05, JPEG" (packet of two), Undated; CD-2203 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Archival Coming-Out Materials, Undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - GAGV Events, 1998-1999 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - GAGV Archive, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - News Clippings, 2000-2006 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - GAGV News Articles, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Old Info (Jim Ver Steeg), 2003 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      primarily GAGV info and newsclippings
    - Empty Closet Articles, Undated (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Empty Closet Distribution Tracking Form, Undated (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Jeff Stryker Action Figure, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Press release packet, Undated; CD-2204 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - A Provider's Introduction to Substance Abuse Treatment for LGBT Individuals, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      US Department of Health and Human Services, Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration, Center for Substance Abuse Treatmet
    - Fundraising Packet, Undated (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Hairspray Gayla, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Town Meeting Materials, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Fliers and Handouts, Undated (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Flyers, Pamphlets, and Brochures, Undated (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Fliers, Pamphlets, and Booklets, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - News clippings and program materials, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 39)
      Includes correspondence and fliers
    - What the Bible Says About Homosexuality, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 40)
      Booklet by Eloise May, written 1997
    - News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - News clippings, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Events, Workshops & Articles, April-September 2005 (Box 56, Folder 43)
    - Newsletters, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Notes & Membership Lists, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Contact Lists, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - Organization List (with contacts), Undated (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - Rochester Area Resource List, Undated (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - The Rochester Transgender Group, Undated (Box 56, Folder 48)
    - Media Contacts, Undated (Box 56, Folder 49)
    - Fliers and Announcements, 1999-2004 (Box 56, Folder 50)
    - Gay & Gray: LGBTQ Senior Housing, Undated (Box 56, Folder 51)
    - Rainbow Train, 2001-2004 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Rainbow Seniors, 2002-2005 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - LGBTQ Elders, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - LGBTQ Elders: Sage Conference, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - LGBTQ Elders: Information & Guides, 2003-2004 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - LGBTQ Elders: Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - LGBTQ Elders: Reference Materials, 2002-2005 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - American Society on Aging, 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - SAGE Materials, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Gay & Gray in the West, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - HIV/Vaccine Trials, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      Regarding Todd Plank's participation in study
    - NYS Dept. of Health HIV/AIDS Training, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - HIV/AIDS Resource Directory, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - LGBTQ Healthcare, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Negotiating the Rochester Health Care System: How Lesbians' Selection Methods and Disclosure Patterns Affect their Health Care Experiences, September 2002 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      Master's Essay by Amanda Lynn Strongczek, University of Rochester
    - Improving Your Sexual IQ (Planned Parenthood), October 2004 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - 3rd Annual Business Education Forum & Community Leadership Luncheon, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Equality Leadership Conference, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Equality Leadership Conference, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Equality Leadership Conference, 2006-2007 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Equality Leadership Conference - Photos, 2007; CD-2365 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual & Transgender Awareness at Kodak, Undated (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - LGBT Awareness at Kodak, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - LGBT Awareness at Kodak (Manual & Addendum), Undated (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Lambda Educational Event at Kodak, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Lambda Network at Kodak, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Requests for Info, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Room Use Guidelines, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Doggie Drag Registration Forms, Undated (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Symposium on Youth & Career Fair, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Presentation & GAGV Information, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - Task Force on Gay, Lesbian, Transgender Bias Report and Recommendations, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 31)
      Presentation to Rochester City School District
    - Pride Week, 2003-2004 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - Pride Picnic and Pride Week, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Court Training Materials, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Rochester Religious Coalition for Equal Marriage, March 2004 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Contact Info, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      Contains information about members of support groups
    - Correspondence, December 2003- August 2004 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Community Center Checklists, Aug-04 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Community Center Checklists, November-December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Marriage Equality 101, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      Evaluations
    - Marriage Equality 101, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      Presentation
    - Same-Sex Marriage Materials, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Same-Sex Marriage Newsclippings, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Youth & Student Related Materials, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Youth Related Materials Packet, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Information for Parents, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Positive Youth Development, Undated (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Outside Organizations: Press Releases and Information, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Outside Organizations & Conference, 2004-2005 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Multi-Faith Roundtable, February 2005 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Second Annual Pride Shabbat, Undated (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Unions & Sexual Diversity Across Nations (selections from the book), Undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - The Lesbian & Gay Big Apple Corps Calendar, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - GAGV Agency Reports, October-November 2003 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Staff Retreat, July 2004 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - News clippings & GAGV Volunteer Material, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - GAGV -- Financial & Job Description, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      Description for Community Education Outreach Coordinator
    - GAGV Events -- Newsclippings, c. 2004 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - GAGV Info, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      Job descriptions, mission statemtent and policies, staff info, volunteer lists, financial info
    - GAGV Committees, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Drafts, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - GAGV Misc., 2003-2007 (Box 58, Folder 29)
      Openings, public relations, technology committee minutes
    - Correspondence & Flyers, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - ImageOUT Correspondence, July 2004 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Community Center Usage, April-June 2004 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Community Center Usage, July 2004 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Coming Out Workshop, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - Community Center Group Memberships, Undated (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Todd Plank Coming Out Workshops, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - MOCHA Project, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Anti-Violence Project, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Todd Plank, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 39)
      Primarily thank-you notes
    - GaySource Info-Line, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - Presentation Request Form, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - Greater Rochester Diversity Council/Diversity, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 42)
    - The Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual & Transgender Community Center, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 43)
    - Theater Programs, Undated (Box 58, Folder 44)
    - Collaboration, c. 2004 (Box 58, Folder 45)
    - Mains for Mayor Archive, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 46)
    - National Lesbian & Gay Journalists Association, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 47)
    - AIDS Rochester Annual Report, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 48)
    - Capital Pride, 2005-2006 (Box 58, Folder 49)
    - CDs Found with Todd Plank Files, 2005-2006, Undated (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - ELC Acks Reg, 2006; CD-2200 (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - ELC, 2005; CD-2201 (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - Our House Tickets, Undated (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - Mains for Mayor Photos, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 51)
    - Youth Event Photos, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 52)
- Series II: Events, Projects, and Services
  - 1971-1984
    - Gay Community Services Project
      - CETA (Comprehensive Employment and Training Act) Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
      - CETA Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Urban League monthly reports, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Monthly report forms, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Monthly reports, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Outreach for CETA, Rick Dixon, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - CETA 1979- Rick, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - CETA, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - CETA- Daryl Clemens, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Tax forms, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Project Equality (Urban League, CETA), 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - CETA/Payroll account, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Urban League Procedures Manual, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - CETA Agreement, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Monthly reports to the Urban League, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - CETA information, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - EAS Payroll information, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - CETA training reimbursement request forms, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
      - CETA tuition reimbursement form, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Personnel policy statement, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Urban League, CETA info- blank forms, monthly reports, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - The Empty Closet
      - Correspondence re: payroll checks for the editor, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Report on duplicator, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Advertising materials, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Price list of mimeo services, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Finance report, June, July 1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Rental agreement, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Subscription requests, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Advertising sales reports, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Rochester Patriot paid receipts, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - "Rosie's" account payable, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Address changes and deletions, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Story submission, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Bankruptcy form?, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Requests, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Editor position resignation correspondence, 1984, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Revenue, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Downtowner Publications bills, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Empty Closet New Account Applications, Undated (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - General
      - Volunteer information, Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Volunteer job application form, Undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Volunteer hours record form, Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Volunteer hours- evenings, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - Volunteer hours- evening, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Volunteer forms, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Volunteer questionnaire, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Lesbian Resource Center, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - LRC meeting structure, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - LRC meeting format, Undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - LRC financial records, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - GAGV library records, Undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - List of "Books to be Reviewed", Undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Picnic financial files, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - Gay Community Picnic finance summary, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Community Picnic press, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Picnic financial files, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - Food service, 1981, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Picnic, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - The Body Politic picnic advertisement, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Picnic financial statements, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - Ice Skating Rink rental contract, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Prom, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Counseling, Undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - Peer counseling committee, 1974, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Peer counseling committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Peer counselors list, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - Peer counseling policy proposal, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 71)
      - Peer counselor materials, 1981? (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Speakers Bureau True & amp; False questions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Speakers Bureau handouts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Speakers Bureau engagement request forms, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Speakers Bureau- engagements fulfilled, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Speakers Bureau- filled engagements, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Speakers Bureau forms, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Trull and Wilson concert, 2/6/1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Trull concert planning materials, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Employers' Survey on gay hiring practices responses, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
      - Referral list summary, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Referral list, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Referral list responses, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - "Alphabetic organization list", 1972-1973? (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Long distance blue list, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Social services lists, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Weekly coffeehouse report, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - GAGV event flyers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - GAGV "Laser Celebration" Benefit flyer, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Coffeehouse flyers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - GAGV event flyers, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Picnic flyer/banner, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Benefit concert flyers/program, June 21, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - GAGV flyers, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Vinnie Cup Awards flyer, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Vinnie Cup news clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Artists for Art Displays, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Blood Drive information, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Buck Anita, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - City Council Candidate List, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Class Contracts (Sign Language & amp; Disco), Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Feedback- mental health agencies, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - GAGV Bulletin Board clippings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - VD flyers/GAGV clinic, Undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - GAGV Newsletter, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - GAGV Gay Community Meeting, Nov. 21, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Gay Happenings in Rochester, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Gay events, 1974? (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - Gay events-local, 1975, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - Women's events, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - Gay legislation, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - Gay organizations-general, 1973-1975, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Gay Youth project, Undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Gay Youth info., 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Housing, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Human Rights Municipal Code, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Human Rights Municipal Code- Rochester, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Lobbying, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - March on Washington Regional Conference, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - March on Washington, 1974, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - March on Washington, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Media Monitor forms, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Homophobia in the Media, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Media- media outlets, correspondence, manuals and guides for dealing with media homophobia, etc., 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous media materials, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous media materials, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous gay liberation related proposals, flyers, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Monroe County Comission on Human Relations, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
      - Monroe County Legal Assistance, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Neighborhood Association, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Planned Parenthood film list, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Polls and Surveys, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Rally for Rights, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Rally for Rights album, Sept. 23, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Referral proposal from GAGV to Wester Monroe Mental Health Center, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Rochester Bail Fund statement of purpose, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Rochester on the move- notes on calendar of events, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Support statement information, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 26-27)
      - University Year for Action, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - University Year for Action, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - University Year for Action proposals, originals, notices, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Victimless crimes, Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Women's groups/services, 1975-1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Writing letters, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Gay Pride Fest '81 schedule-Buffalo, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Posters, Undated (Mapcase-folder 1)
        "The Rochester Gay Men's Gathering Presents Between Men", Undated; "Mattachine Society DANCE On Board the USS Little Rock", July 4th, no year; "Summer Days Gay Dance: Celebrate International Gay Pride Weekend in Canada"
      - Phone logs, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Phone logs, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Phone logs, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Phone logs, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Phone logs, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Counseling forms, log sheets, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Volunteer hours- day (phone logs), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Office logs, 3/77-12-78 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Phone logs, 1979 or 1983? (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Women's logs, 1/78-10/79 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Logs, 1/79-11/79 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Phone logs- days, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Phone logs- days, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Peer counseling, mens evenings logs, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Daily staff logs- phone questions, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Peer counseling log- women's, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Peer counselor/FAC logs, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
      - Daily staff phone logs, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Daily staff phone logs, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Phone logs analysis/study, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Phone log breakdowns, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Phone logs, Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Political Work
      - Monroe County Board of Elections, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Political-legal, 1972? (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Community Chest survey, 1974? (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - County Legislature, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - County Districts 1-14, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - County Districts 15-29, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - County Clerk, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - District Attorney, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Senator Perry, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - County Court Judges, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - City Council, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - NYS Assembly, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - NYS Senate, 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - NYS Officials, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - NYS Representatives, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 42)